嘿 你正好撞见我清洗这个血淋淋的厕所啦
Oh, hi there, you caught me just mopping up this bloody bathroom.
我觉得我干得不错
I think I did a pretty good job.
我用了拖布
I used the mop, and...
呃 所以我想知道我现在能回家了吗?
Yeah, basically, I was wondering if I could go home now.
好吧 多谢了
OK, great, thanks very much.
那我要不要去... 主持节目?
Should I host the show?
哦 好吧 那我就去主持节目啦
Oh, you mean serious? Okay, great, I'll go host the show then.
跟我来
Here, follow me.
对了 看呐 这儿的一切都是假的
Oh yeah, see it's just... Everything is fake here.
#我弄不掉身上的毛发#
#I can't get this hair off me#
#因为我被狼咬了#
#I was bit by a wolf you see#
#如果我只是个某某人的话#
#Actually if I have just been some guy#
#对啊 我猜就只是某个人而已#
#Yeah that's right guess they were just some guy#
听译/时间轴/后期: 二骚
主题曲灵感来自:
嘿最近咋样? 我就像饶舌歌手一样说道
What's up? I say, like a rapping person might.
欢迎来到少狼After After Show
And welcome to the Teen Wolf After After Show,
一个在节目之后的之后的节目
a show so after and after show
他们甚至不能在电视上给我们找个时间段播放
they couldn't even find a spot for it on television,
即使我要求过他们了
despite the fact that I asked.
我是主持人Morgan Evans
I'm your host Morgan Evans,
我本来要告诉你们Derek Hale的生日的
and I was going to tell you all Derek Hale's birthday,
但有人发推让我去用火烧死自己
but then someone twitted at me to go die on a fire.
所以我是不会告诉你们的了
So that's not happening.
不过 年轻的Derek Hale出现了!
You know what it is though, young Derek Hale!
谁能想到他也曾经是个孩子?
Who knew he was ever a child?
我肯定没想到过
I certainly didn't.
到了连线在少狼片场的Sam Childs的时候了
Alright now it's time to check in with Sam Childs out there on the set of Teen Wolf,
让我们来看看他的本周一刻是什么吧
with his Moment of the Week.
#哦耶#
#Oh yeah#
#你知道现在是什么时候了#
#You know what time it is#
#是本周一刻时间啦#
#It's time for Moment of the Week#
大家好我是Sam Childs 少狼的制作总监
Hey I'm Sam Childs, I'm the Production Supervisor on Teen Wolf.
这周最疯狂的时刻之一是
And one of the craziest moments of this episode was,
我们在拍摄高中场景的外景地
when we were at our location we shoot our exterior high school stuff at,
很多粉丝都出现在那里
and there were a lot of fans that showed up,
因为那是个公共场所
because it's a public place,
我们就得把我们当时还没有公开的
and we had to move our secret Berserker characters
狂战士角色们从他们的等待区
who were not revealed yet between their holding area and
用毯子盖住 移动到片场
the set with blankets strapped over them,
这样就没人看到他们 我们的秘密也就不会泄露了
so that no one would see them and our secrets wouldn't get out.
MTV又一次逼我连线在片场的Nicole Byer
Once again MTV is making me go out to Nicole Byer who's in the field.
-上帝啊 开始吧 -你们好呀!
-God, here we go. -Hola, hola!
我在墨西哥一家夜店的里屋
I'm in the back room of a club in Mexico
我男朋友Stiles就是在这儿拿出很多钱 对墨西哥人说
where my boyfriend Stiles brought a ton of money to the Mexicans to be like,
把Derek还给我 他是我朋友!
give me back Derek, he's my friend!
我会很乐意让Stiles
I would love for Stiles
在我巨大柔软的**上下雨
to make it rain, on my big pillow-y...
我们不应该这么做
We should not do this.
我们不应该再让Nicole出现在节目里
We should not have Nicole on the show anymore.
让我们参观一下这个夜店吧
Let's take a look around this club.
那儿有本有趣的书
There's a fun book.
那儿有西班牙语叫做"水果"的东西
There's what the Spanish call "frugt.*"
西班牙语里找不到她发音的词 这个词来自丹麦语
还有椅子 那里还有一些[哔——]
There's chairs, and there's a bunch of **** over here!
这是什么?
What is this?
喔哦!
Uh-oh, uh-oh!
我可以把我的男朋友Stiles钩在上面
I could hook my boyfriend Stiles up to this,
-这样他就不能从我巨大的黑**中逃走了 -好了 谢谢Nicole 那真是有趣啊
-so he can't escape my big black... -Great, thanks Nicole, that was fun.
-果然在我意料之中 -再见!
-Where exactly as I expected. -Good-bye!
笨手笨脚的人并不容易
You know, being clumsy is difficult.
下面就让我们来看看少狼片场里的一些笨拙的人吧
Please take a look of some clumsy people from the set of Teen Wolf.
少狼片场里最笨手笨脚的人... 大概是我了
Clumsiest person on the Teen Wolf set... Probably me.
片场里除了我之外最笨手笨脚的人...
Clumsiest person on set besides me...
-是Holland. -Holland. -Holland...
-Holland. -Holland. -Holland...
是片场里最笨手笨脚的人了 毫无疑问
is the clumsiest person on set, without a doubt.
对了 其实Holland也很笨手笨脚的
You know what, actually Holland is pretty clumsy too.
我认为大家比她都差远了
I don't even think anyone comes close.
我看她被绊到和撞上门很多次了
I have seen her trip and run into a door at least a handful of times.
当她就正常地走路 面前没有任何障碍物的时候
When she's just walking normally with nothing in her path,
她看起来还是随时可能摔倒的样子
she looks like she's falling down.
我不能好好走路 我脑袋有点问题
I can't walk, something's wrong with my brain,
我的下丘脑有些问题
my hypothalamus needs some help.
她会被任何东西绊到
She'll just trip up on anything.
她说 %^&*(^# 我就说 啥?
She's just like, %^&*(^#, and I go, I go, what?
%^& 日本 &*^#&%^& 如果我能说对的话
%^&, Japanese &*^#&, if I get to even say that correctly.
弯腰 弯腰 弯腰?
Stoop, stoop, stoop?
等等 说不通啊
No wait, that... doesn't make sense?
我们的"关须"*应该是...
Our "resolation" should be like...
她想说"关系"
哦对 用有*...
Oh right, pozzess...
她想说"拥有"
他 嗯哼 对 那就是答案了
He, um-huh, yep, that's the answer.
我能再来一遍吗
Can I start that over?
因为我们有很多&*^$%^& 很多%^&^(* 嗯
'Cause we've got much &*^$%^&, much %^&^(*, yeah.
^&*$^(%@# [哔——] 我今天能说话吗
^&*$^(%@#, ****, can I get to talk today?
在桑迪... 在德克萨斯 圣安东尼奥 我都不能读字了
In Sandie... San Antonio, Texas. I can't read.
什么都有毛病 说话有问题
It's an everything problem. It's a talking problem...
加减有问题
It's an adding problem...
我的时间管理能力能变得更好
I don't think that time... my management time skills could improve,
我的灵敏度有提高的余地
my dexterity could improve,
我的运气也可以变好
my luck could improve,
有很多我可以提高的东西
there's a lot of things I could improve.
除了我的笨手笨脚 我不需要更多的笨拙了
Aside my clumsiness I don't need to improve that.
别走开! 别走开!
Stay tuned! Stay tuned!
早些时候有人问我 嘿现在到节目中的什么时候了
Earlier, someone was like, hey what time of the show is it,
答案是到了采访Linden的时候啦
and the answer is time to interview Linden.
还有我的朋友 我特别的朋友 他刚走进了背景里
And my friend, my special friend, who just walked into the background.
-我觉得Daniel Sharman刚刚离开了 -Son of a bitch
-I think Daniel Sharman just left. -Son of a bitch.
我一直以为他是副骨架呢
I thought he's a skeleton this entire time.
-可以开始问问题了吗? -当然了 请吧 -很好
-Should we get into some questions? -Please, let's. -Okay, great.
在你儿子上一季干了这么多可怕的事之后 你看他的眼神会不会奇怪?
Do you think you look at your son weird since he like pull all the shit last season?
-我只是很高兴他回来了 -嗯
-I think I'm incredibly happy to have him back. -Right.
-你知道那不是他 -那是个不同的人 只是脸一样而已 -那不是他
-You know it wasn't him. -It's a different kid. With the same face. -It wasn't him.
嗯 就像你有个很糟糕的孪生兄弟一样
Yeah. It'd be like if you had a crappy twin.
-对的 -嗯
-Yeah. -Yeah.
你认为他们把Parrish副警长加进来是来帮助你的吗 因为你一直都压力很大?
So do you think they brought Deputy Parrish on to help you since you're so stressed out all the time? Or...
我认为Parrish副警长是...
I think Deputy Parrish is...
我觉得他有很多事情我们都不知道
I think there's a lot going on there that we don't know about.
真的 我认为他有一些什么事情
Truthfully, I think he got some stuff going on.
-嗯 我不知道我是否信任他 -我非常信任他 但我不知道这么做是否明智
-Yeah, I don't know if I trust him. -I trust him, a lot. But I don't know if it's wise to trust him.
-对 -他保护了我好几次
-Right, yes. -You know, he's had my back quite a few times.
-但那可能是一个大计划中的一部分 -可能是 -好吧
-But it could all be part of some master plan. -Could be. -Okay.
下面我要玩一个小游戏
So I'm gonna play a quick game.
-好的 -你在剧里饰演一名警察 -是的
-Okay, go. -So you play a cop on the show, obviously. -I do, I do.
我会给你一些警用通讯代码 然后你告诉我你觉得它们是什么意思
I'm gonna give you some scanner codes, and I want you to tell me what you think they mean.
哦天呐 好吧 开始吧
Oh oh god, okay, go ahead.
有一个470发生了
So this is a... There's a 470.
470是... 有人在暴露自己
A 470 is a... They're exposing themselves.
其实是出现了伪造品
It's actually a forgery.
-哇哦 -是的 -我不知道这个 -比如 这儿有一幅赝品马蒂斯*
-Wow. -Yeah. -I did not know that. -So it's like we've got a fake Matisse.
野兽派创始人及主要代表人
有一副莫迪利亚尼* 但不是真品 这就是470了
There's a Modigliani, that's not real. That's a 470.
表现主义画派的代表艺术家之一
507呢?
Alright, this is a 507.
呃...
Er....
-音乐扰民 -音乐扰民?
-Loud music. -Loud music?
-妨害公众安宁 很相近 -对吧 -干得不错
-Public nuisance. That's pretty close. -There you go. -That's really good, yeah.
就是你说的
That's absolutely what that is.
这个是我的最爱 因为我都不知道怎么会有这种事情 但这是个604
Now this one is my favorite because I can't imagine how this is a thing, but a 604.
604是... 谋杀
604 would be... Murder.
其实是投掷导弹
It's actually throwing missiles.
-什么 有人发射导弹? -对 有人就...
-Now you shoot missiles? -Yeah, so this would be somebody...
把它们扔出栅栏外
Getting rid of them over their fence.
-接下来是一些来自Twitter的问题 -很好 -所以这些问题都很有趣
-So these are some Twitter questions now. -Good, good. -So obviously these are fun.
这个问题来自LuckyYCim
This one's from LuckyYCim,
到目前为止最喜欢的一幕
favorite scene in all seasons that you filmed.
我很爱 Stiles在长曲棍球比赛里表现非常好的那一幕
I really love the scene after Stiles did incredibly well in the lacrosse game,
和他的那一幕
and that scene with him.
-他是你的好儿子 -对 -真棒
-That's your boy. -Yeah. -That's great.
这个问题来自anselsinfinity
This is from anselsinfinity,
你能做出的最奇怪的面部表情是什么
which is what's the weirdest face expression you cal pull.
几天前我骑着自行车
I was riding my bike the other day, actually,
骑到了路边上
and I got on the side of the road,
然后突然间我就要撞上一个后视镜了 我就发现我的表情是这样
and suddenly I'm about to hit a rear-view mirror and I found myself going
-啊啊啊啊啊 -不错的表情
-Ahhhhhhh. -That's good.
我的大概就是这个
Yeah, mine is probably this one.
这个问题来自Alysa
Alright, this one's from Alysa,
她问 从一到兔子宝宝的范围里 Dylan O'Brien的头发是多软?
who says on the scale of one to baby rabbits, how soft is Dylan O'Brien's hair?
他头上抹了东西吗 还是没抹?
I mean, does he have product in the hair, or no product in the hair?
我觉得应该就是只用了洗发水和护发素吧
I think we're saying just shampoo, just conditioning.
噢那真是华丽 丝一般地柔软
Oh it's luxurious, I mean, it's silky.
-所以我觉得是五只兔子宝宝 -五只兔子宝宝这么软
-So I guess it'd be a five-rabbit. -It'd be a five baby rabbits.
-很好 -对 就是丝一般绝赞
-Great. -Yeah, just silky goodness.
Valarie想知道 如果你可以给这个节目重新命名的话 你会把它叫做什么?
Valarie wants to know if you could rename the show, what would you call it?
Linden Ashby Show
Linden Ashby Show.
-很好 欢迎来到Linden Ashby Show -对
-That's great. Welcome to the Linden Ashby Show. -Yes.
很好很好
Yeah, that's great.
别走开! 别走开!
Stay Tuned! Stay Tuned!
-你想玩Gif-Bait吗? -当然 -好
-Now would you like to do play a fun game and do some Gif-Baits? -Please. -Alright, sweet.
-你觉得你是个摇滚明星 还是什么? -不 我是名恐龙训练师
-Do you think you're a rock star, or what's going on? -No, I'm a dinosaur trainer.
-你愿意让大家看下面这个片段吗? -当然 我们要看什么?
-Do you mind throwing to a clip? -No, what are we watching?
-你可以就说 来看这个片段吧 -嘿 来看这个片段吧
-You can just say, here, watch this clip. -Hey, watch this clip.
我见过最多的少狼纹身是三曲枝
The most common Teen Wolf tattoo that I see is the Triskele.
我对纹少狼纹身很能感同身受
I can totally relate to people getting Teen Wolf tattoos,
我纹的时候就毫不犹豫
I don't even blink when they do it to me.
我知道粉丝们有多忠实
I know how loyal the fans are,
他们多欣赏 喜欢这部剧
and how much they appreciate the show and love the show.
而且我听说过这部剧改变人们生活的故事
And I've heard how it changes people's lives.
我纹的第一个少狼纹身是这个
The first Teen Wolf tattoo I got is this one,
是个正在嚎叫的狼 里面有个三曲枝
and it's a howling wolf with a Triskele in it.
我们俩当时决定一起纹少狼纹身 狼群纹身
The two of us decided to get Teen Wolf tattoos together, pack tattoos.
我是因为她喜欢上少狼的 所以我把她认作我的Alpha
I got into Teen Wolf because of her, so I kind of think of her as my Alpha.
我身上有一个Alpha纹身
I got the Alpha tattoo on me.
Jeff Davis是我的偶像 我想给电视剧写剧本
Jeff Davis is my idol. I wanna write for television.
所以我纹了这个 意在提醒自己以后年龄大些时想做的事情
So I kind of got it as more of a reminder of what I wanna do when I'm older.
这个纹身的灵感来自Scott的纹身 而Scott的纹身灵感来自这个纹身
This is inspired from Scott's tattoo which is inspired from this one.
说得通吗?
Does that make any sense?
在那一集里 Scott想了一个纹身 他画了一个圈 然后在里面又画了个圈
In the episode Scott inspires a tattoo and he draws a circle and a circle in between it,
这就是她纹的 超酷 谢谢你
and that's what she got. It's so cool. So thank you.
-谢谢你 -我很感激 -不用谢 -你很赞
-Thank you. -I appreciate it. -You're welcome. -You're awesome.
我几乎是在Allison死后马上纹的这个纹身
I got this tattoo pretty much right after Allison died.
我手指上有枝为了Allison Argent纹的箭
I actually have an arrow for Allison Argent on my finger right there.
这是为了Allison纹的
This is for Allison.
我的纹身是个三曲枝 Hale家的标志
My tattoo is a Triskele, the Hale Family symbol.
还有一句话 做你自己的精神支柱
And then there's be your own anchor.
当Mellisa McCall说了"做你自己的精神支柱"之后
When Mellisa McCall said "be your own anchor,"
我立刻就发短信 打电话给我的纹身师了
I immediately was like texting and calling my tattoo artist.
我在"做你自己的支柱"这句话在剧里被说出来之后立刻决定要纹个少狼纹身
I decided to get a Teen Wolf tattoo immediately after be your own anchor was said on the show.
找到你的精神支柱
Find your anchor.
我的支柱曾经是Allison
My anchor was Allison.
-现在Allison不在我身边了 -那就做你自己的精神支柱
-I don't have Allison anymore. -Then be your own anchor.
我决定纹一个少狼纹身就是在听到那句话的瞬间
The moment I decided to get a Teen Wolf tattoo was literally the moment that I heard that.
我在对Scott说出那句话的时候
You know when I said that to Scott on the show,
我并不知道这会在我们的观众中引起多强的共鸣
I didn't know how much it was gonna resonate with our audience.
Jeff其实是从与他母亲的对话中提取出的这句话
Jeff actually pulled from a talk that he had with his mom for that particular speech.
我记得在那集之后 很多人说都被那句话感动了
And I remember after that episode a lot of people said they were moved by that.
这句话提醒我做我自己
It just reminds me everyday to just be... Me.
一些粉丝还问过我对他们纹这个纹身怎么想
A couple of fans have actually asked what do you think of me getting this tattoo?
然后发照片给我看
You know and they'll send some flash with it.
我都会说 你确定吗?
And I always say are you sure?
因为这可是永久性的
'Cause it's forever.
我们肯定会纹更多的少狼纹身的
Probably will definitely get more Teen Wolf tattoos.
我想在我小臂上纹个狼人相关的纹身
I would really like to get a werewolf pop reference on my forearm.
我觉得这很棒 赞透了 请继续
I think it's great. It's awesome. Please, keep them coming.
嘿 你知道每次你向喷泉里扔一枚硬币许愿
Hey did you know that every time you throw a coin into a fountain,
AT&T的某个人就会走过来 拿起它 然后把它变成现实吗?
someone from AT&T comes along, grabs it, and turns your wish into reality?
我就知道
I did.
今天的愿望来自Courtney
Today's wish comes from Courtney,
她说她想看演员们说脏话的合集2.0
who said she wants to see a cast swearing compilation 2.0.
好吧Courtney 你的愿望就要实现了 所以接着吧!
Well Courtney, you're getting your wish, so take it!
我最喜欢的脏话大概是[哔——]
My favorite swear word is probably s**t.
我喜欢[哔——]
I like f**k.
我喜欢说[哔——]
I like s**t.
呃 我喜欢[哔——]
Um, I like as****e.
呃 我还喜欢 其实总共没几个脏话词 对吧?
Um, I like, there's not many swear words, huh?!
我就喜欢那个F开头的词
I just like the f-word.
肯定是[哔——]啦
I mean it has to be just f**k.
Mother[哔——]
Motherf***er.
因为可以是[哔——] 或者你生气的时候可以说[哔——]
It could be like f**k, or you can be mad at me like f**k,
这一个词就可以覆盖你想说的很大范围
you know, it could definitely, it can cover the spectrum of things you that need to say in one word.
我其实努力不说脏话
I actually try not to constantly swear,
但有时候自然就发生了
but you know sometimes it happens.
老兄 什么F啊
Oh dude, what the f.
F炸弹 F炸弹 F炸弹*
F-bomb, f-bomb, f-bomb.
都指Fuck
在孩子们身边呆多了 我学到了一个很蠢的
From around kids, I've got a dumb one
就是个脏话替代词
that I say... And it's just my substitute swear word,
就是Sanjay Gupta
which is Sanjay Gupta.
什么哔
What the bleep.
Bitch Bitch Bitch Bitch Bitch
Bitch bitch bitch bitch bitch!
我经常用Bitch这个词 Bitch
I use bitch all the time, bitch.
就像 Bitch 我应该去演绝命毒师
I mean, it's just like bitch, I should have been on Breaking Bad.
这就是你每天少狼剂量的上限啦
That's it for your daily dose of Teen Wolf,
如果你撞到了头不记得看过这个了
and that's of course if you hit your head and don't remember watching this,
还是可以再看一遍的
you can just go watch it again.
听起来很有趣 不是吗?
Yeah that sounds fun, right? Alright,
你还有时间来让我们知道你对今晚这集少狼怎么想
now there's still time for you to let us to know what you thought of tonight's episode of Teen Wolf,
只要登录Instagram
simply log onto Instagram,
上传记录你反应的视频 用#packreacts 这个标签
and upload your fan reaction videos using hashtag #packreacts,
每周三查看mtv.com 看看你有没有被选上
then check mtv.com every Wednesday to see if you've made the cut.
我是Morgan Evans 我有三个漂亮的儿子
I'm Morgan Evans, and I have three beautiful sons.
有一件我们在这季知道的事情
The one thing I think that we do learn this season,
其实我从一开始就这么觉得
is what I've kind of always thought since the beginning
但一直没能确认 就一直这么相信着
and didn't have confirmation of it, but I just believed it,
因为他有台非常好的车 后来还有个很赞的阁楼
'cause he had a very nice car, and ended up having this nice loft,
即使他在开始的两季都无家可归
even though he was like homeless for the first two seasons.
但Derek很富有 Derek有很多钱!
But Derek is loaded. Derek has a lot of money!
这就是我们一起发现的事情
So that's something that we all kind of find out together.